

Hau Zheng Yi Frontend Developer

www.hauzhengyi.github.io

in www.linkedin.com/in/zyhau

**** +6016673158

Yuala Lumpur, Malaysia

PROFILE

A hard-working developer with good attention to detail, who holds himself to high standards in writing quality codes. Experienced in frontend technologies such as JavaScript, Vue, React, Nuxt, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind etc. Communicates well with customers and team members (Mandarin/English), able to learn technologies quickly with minimal guidance. Xiamen University Malaysia Hackathon award winner.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Hytech Consulting Management Sdn Bhd, Software Engineer (Frontend)

Jun 2023 - present

- Integral member of the H5 team, responsible for developing web pages for mobile apps.
- Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Working with backend developers to ensure smooth API integration
- Self-testing before deployment to test environment, fixing possible bugs before publishing to production environment.
- Main technologies used: Nuxt JS, PrimeVue, React, Android Studio.

TDCX (MY) Sdn Bhd, Fontend Developer (Google Project)

May 2022 - May 2023

 Creating, deploying and troubleshooting implementations such as Google Ads conversion tracking, Google Analytics, Google Merchant Center Shopping Feed, Dynamic Remarketing, Ecommerce Tracking, Google Tag Manager, etc. using CMS platforms such as Wordpress, Shopify, Go Daddy, Squarespace and Wix. Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

 Helping sales teams deploy leads, implement tags, optimize ads performance, enable integration and troubleshoot customer's issues regarding their online ad campaigns.

CUSTLR SaratiX, Web Developer Internship

Feb 2022 - May 2022

• Transforming UI/UX designs into beautiful, responsive web pages.

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

- Developed robust backend for e-commerce analytics.
- Skills involved: HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript, Laravel, Bootstrap, jQuery, MySQL.

Sunline Technology (Malaysia) Sdn Bhd, Software Developer Internship

Sep 2021 - Jan 2022

- Implemented application modules under the direction of Senior Developers using in-house custom Java development software.
- Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia

Maintaining and updating large database systems using MySQL.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Technology,

Aug 2019 - Feb 2022

Xiamen University Malaysia

Sepang, Malaysia

- CGPA 3.55 | XMUM Merit Scholarship | Chinese Ambassador Scholarship
- XMUM Hackathon 2021 Topic 1 Winner: Environmental Issues due to Development of Cities

⊗ SKILLS

Vue/Nuxt | React JS | ES6 | JavaScript | jQuery | Bootstrap 5 | HTML5/CSS3 | Tailwind CSS

W LANGUAGES

Hau Zheng Yi hauzhengyi@hotmail.com